If the Church knew of your power, you would be in those cages with them.
Se a Igreja soubesse do seu poder, você também estaria enjaulado.
I said I'd save her.
Eu disse que iria salvá-la!
'Ware the boy! Don't let him escape!
Cuidado com o garoto! Não o deixem escapar!
Halt!
Alto!
I'm following the prisoners!
Eu vou atrás dos prisioneiros!
Stop him!  Get him! After him!
Detenham-no! Atrás dele!
You see Paul, the young folk of today have no vim, no vigour, no lust for li-
Tá vendo, Paul? Esses jovens de hoje não tem vigor, amor à vid..
Hey!
Ei!
By the Light!
Santa Luz!
What has spilled its tainted fire here, My servant?
Quem derramou sangue impuro aqui, Meu servo?
Lord, I wish only to serve you.
Senhor, eu só desejo servi-Lo.
Where is My sacrifice?
Onde está Minha oferenda?
Are these My sacrifices?
São esses a Minha oferenda?
You may not look on his grace.
Vocês não podem olhá-lo.
Leave.
Saiam.
I may not lie to you, Lord.
Eu não posso mentir, Senhor.
We have no sacrifice.
Não temos oferendas.
Then you have no further use for My blessings, My servant?
Então você não tem mais uso para Minha bençãos, servo?
We apologise most humbly, Lord.
Nos desculpamos humildemente, Senhor.
On the next sacrifice day, we will pay you this sacrifice thrice over what was to be here.
No próximo sacrifício, traremos três vezes mais do que deveria ter aqui hoje.
Three times?
Três vezes?
The sacrifice was promised today.
As oferendas foram prometidas para hoje.
Yes, my Lord. But- We were attacked.
Sim, meu Senhor. Mas.. nós fomos atacados.
Of course you were. You cannot hide such things from Me.
Claro que foram. Não há como esconder isso de Mim.
Yes, my Lord.
Sim, Senhor.
You were smote with tainted fire. By this... man-child.
Vocês foram vencidos pelo fogo impuro daquele.. jovem.
You will bring him as your sacrifice.
Você o trará como oferenda.
Lord, I- I am not-
Senhor, Eu.. Eu não..
What is his name?
Qual é o nome dele?
I fear we do not know his name, my Lord.
Temo não saber, meu Senhor.
No matter.
Não importa.
You will bring him to Me, will you not?
Você o trará até Mim, não é?
Yes, my Lord.
Sim, Senhor.
We will.
Trarei.
I say! Surely it isn't Thursday yet?
Nossa! Não sabia que hoje era dia de Gala Gay!
Wh- Where are the privvies?
Onde fica o banheiro?
Thanks!
Valeu!
It would kill you to have a window?
Por que nunca tem janela?
Hey!
Ei!
You're that fellow the Monks are chasing!
Você é o cara que os Monges estão perseguindo!
In here!
Aqui!
Where did he go?
Onde ele foi?
Uh?
Heim?
The heretic.
O herege.
Answer me!
Responda!
He's in my bed.
Ele está na minha cama.